// Quesitons for Star Wars Category
// One object for each question

const swQuestions = [
   
   {
      "question" : "What model is the Millennium Falcon?",
      "correctAns" : "Corellian YT-1300f Light Freighter",
      "multChoice" : ["Corellian CR90 Corvette", "Kuat EF76 Nebulon-B Escort Frigate", "Corellian YT-1300f Light Freighter", "ST-70 Assault Ship", "Corellian VCX0-100 Light Freighter"]
   },
   
   {
      "question" : "What is the name of the Wookie home planet?",
      "correctAns" : "Kashyyyk",
      "multChoice" : ["Endor", "Kashyyyk", "Ilum", "Dathomir", "Crait"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "What species is Ahsoka Tano?",
      "correctAns" : "Togruta",
      "multChoice" : ["Togruta", "Zabrak", "Twi'lek", "Rodian", "Iktochi"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "On which planet did Darth Vader establish his base?",
      "correctAns" : "Mustafar",
      "multChoice" : ["Crait", "Jedha", "Naboo", "Utapau", "Mustafar"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "According to Dexter Jettser in Attack of the Clones, what do the analysis droids at the Jedi temple focus on?",
      "correctAns" : "Symbols",
      "multChoice" : ["Smell", "Materials", "Particulate Matter", "Symbols", "Digital Cookies"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "What cell number is Leah Organa in when Luke and Han rescue her from the Death Star (Hint: It is also Finn's Stormtrooper ID number)?",
      "correctAns" : "2187",
      "multChoice" : ["7567", "5555", "2187", "2224", "1409"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "What is Luke Skywalker's callsign at the Battle of Yavin?",
      "correctAns" : "Red-5",
      "multChoice" : ["Blue-2", "Red-5", "Green-7", "Black-Leader", "Gold-1"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "Which was not a ship taking part in the Rebel attack over Endor?",
      "correctAns" : "K-Wing",
      "multChoice" : ["X-Wing", "Y-Wing", "B-Wing", "A-Wing", "K-Wing"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "What creature do Tusken Raiders ride in the deserts of Tatooine?",
      "correctAns" : "Bantha",
      "multChoice" : ["Tauntaun", "Bantha", "Acklay", "Grinjer", "Boga"]
   },

   {
      "question" : "Which Sith Lord created the 'Rule of Two'?",
      "correctAns" : "Darth Plagueis",
      "multChoice" : ["Darth Bane", "Darth Revan", "Darth Sidious", "Darth Tyranus", "Darth Plagueis"]
   },

]

export{
   swQuestions
}